Welcome friends to Krish Official.
In this video, we will discuss the
ICC Lombard stock.
Currently, the stock is trading around the 1332 level. We will
try to understand what action should be taken with this
stock from here. You
can see that I have opened the chart on a daily basis here. The
stock is currently trading at its 20m level
and well above its
20m level, which is at 1251, and
is well away from its 200m level, which is
at 1160. You can see that the
stock has also left a large gap near this level.
What happens in such a situation is that the
stock tries to close this gap for a while,
and currently, the
stock is trading around its resistance level. If
you
look at the anchor chart here, you can easily understand
that until the stock sustains above 1340,
that too with good volume, the
stock will have an upward trend.  You
can see the face of consolidation
and the histogram is also forming an upward trend. There is
high momentum in ITM as well, which is currently
around 66 and C is around 87, which
according to the complete, is also showing positive strength.
All the indicators are currently at their highest levels
and if you open this chart on a weekly basis,
then you will see that all the
indicators are at their highest point, so it is possible that
you may see a sideways or upward move in the stock for now.
Even if there is a rally, then a very sharp rise should
not be expected. Now if we talk about the
levels, if the stock
breaks the first support level of 1300, then the
stock can see levels up to 1270 on the downside. The
stock will see a rise only
when the stock
breaks the level of 1340 on the upside, then
you can also see levels up to 380 in it.
My thinking is that
whoever has taken a position here should book a profit for once.  Have you
made a stock or added it to your portfolio for the long term? You should
not take an aggressive position immediately. So, that's all
for now. See you
in the next video. If you like the
video, please like, share and subscribe.